Bingo !
( chimps screeching )
Fucking hell .
( screech )
- Oh , God ... - Keep your shit together .
If you wanna get ' em out of here .
- I can pop these , no problem . - So get to it !
Security , we have a break-in . Get the ...
I know who you are . I know what you think ...
lf you don 't wanna get hurt , keep your mouth shut and don 't move .
The chimps are infected .
They 're highly contagious . They 've been given an inhibitor .
- infected with what ? - To cure , you must first understand .
lnfected with what ?
Rage .
- What is he talking about ? - Get the cages open .
No ! No ! No !
Listen , you sick bastard , we 're taking your torture victims with us .
We 'II get you out of here .
The animals are contagious . The infection is in their blood and saliva . One bite ...
Stop ... Stop ! You 've no idea !
( screaming )
Get it off ! help me !
Get it off ! Get it off !
- What 's the matter with her ? - You have to kill her !
( screams ) Oh , my God !
- What 's the matter with her ? - We have to kill her now !
Oh , God ...
( screaming )
( sharp intake of breath )
hello ?
( coughs )
( Iouder ) hello !
( beIches )
hello ?
hello !
( alarm )
hello ?
( noises from behind door )
( gasping and retching )
Father ?
Father , are you OK ?
Oh , shouldn 't have done that .
ShouIdn 't have done that .
Shit !
( man ) Over here !
- Over here ! - Come on !
Go , go , go !
Keep going !
- What the fuck is going on ? - Just shut up !
- Covered everything . - Who are those people ?
Let 's go ! Let 's go !
- What the fuck is going on ? - Just move !
Come on !
Man walks into a bar with a giraffe . They each get pissed .
The giraffe faIIs over .
The man goes to leave and the barman says " Oi ! You can 't leave that lying there . "
He says " No , it 's not a Iion. lt 's a giraffe " .
He 's completely humorless .
You two should get on like a house on fire .
So who are you ?
You 're from the hospital .
- Are you a doctor ? - He 's not a doctor . He 's a patient .
I 'm a bicycle courier .
I was riding a package from Farringdon to Shaftesbury Avenue
and a car cut across me .
Then I wake up today in hospital . I wake up and I 'm ...
I 'm hallucinating or I 'm ...
What 's your name ?
Jim .
I 'm Mark . This is SeIena .
OK , Jim .
I 've got some bad news .
It started as rioting , and right from the beginning you knew this was different .
Because it was happening in small villages , market towns .
And then it wasn 't on the TV anymore .
It was in the street outside . It was coming through your windows .
It was a virus .
An infection .
You didn 't need a doctor to tell you that .
It was the blood .
There was something in the blood .
By the time they tried to evacuate the cities , it was already too late .
The infection was everywhere .
The army bIockades were overrun .
And that 's when the exodus started .
The day before broadcasting stopped ,
there were reports of infection in Paris and New York .
We didn 't hear anything more after that .
- What 's the government doing ? - There 's no government .
Of course there 's a government !
There 's always a government . They 're in a bunker or a plane ...
No , there 's no government , no police , no army .
No TV , no radio , no electricity .
You 're the first uninfected person we 've seen in six days .
Where 's your family ?
They 're dead . Like SeIena 's .
Yours will be dead too .
Look , I have to find them . They live in Deptford. I can walk it . OK ?
You 'II go and come back , yeah ?
- You won 't . - Yes !
No one ever comes back .
So lesson one .
You never go anywhere alone unless you 've got no choice .
Lesson two .
only travel during daylight . unless you 've got no choice .
We 'II take you tomorrow .
We 'II all go and find your dead parents together , OK ?
Eat .
If you want her to slow down , you 'II have to say .
- lf there 's anyone ... - l understand .
- Anyone ... - l understand !
OK .
( sniffs )
Jim ...
Wait !
They died peacefully . You should be grateful .
I 'm not grateful .
My ...
parents and my sister , we went to Paddington Station ,
hoping maybe we could get on a plane , maybe we could buy our way onto a plane .
I remember my dad had all this cash ,
even though cash was completely useless .
About 20,000 other people had the same idea .
Crowd was surging .
I lost my grip on my sister 's hand .
I remember the ground was soft .
I Iooked down and I was standing on all these people .
Like a carpet . people who had fallen and ...
Somewhere in the crowd there were lnfected. lt spread fast .
No one could run . AII you could do was climb .
climb over more people . So I did that. I climbed .
And I got up on top of this kiosk .
Looking down , you couldn 't tell which faces were infected and which weren 't .
Then I saw my dad . Not my mum or my sister .
My dad .
His face ...
selena 's right . You should be grateful .
We don 't have time to get back to the shop before dark . We should stay here tonight .
My room 's up at the top . You two can have that .
No , we 'II all sleep in the same room . It 's safer .
( radio )
Jim .
- You 're back . - Yeah .
- How was it ? - Fine .
Give me a drink of that , will ya ?
- lt 's empty . - Ha !
Here .
I 'll start working on them , then .
Mark ! Mark !
selena ! help !
( SeIena ) lt 's clear .
- That 's Mr Bridges . - Were you bitten ?
And his daughter . From four doors down .
- Were you bitten ? - No .
Did any of the blood get in your mouth ?
No .
Mark ?
Wait ...
( Mark screams )
Get that cleaned off .
Do you have any clothes here ?
Um ... I ... Yes .
Then get them and get dressed . We have to leave now .
More infected will be coming . They always do .
( Jim ) How did you know ? How did you know he was infected ?
- The blood . - There was blood on me. lt was on you .
I didn 't know he was infected . He knew. I couId see it in his face .
If someone gets infected , you 've about 20 seconds to kill them .
It might be your brother , your sister or your oldest friend. lt makes no difference .
Just so you know where you stand , if it happens to you , I 'II do it in a heartbeat .
He was full of plans . Have you got any plans , Jim ?
Do you want us to find a cure and save the world or just fall in love and fuck ?
plans are pointless .
Staying alive 's as good as it gets .
Hey , hey , hey , hey .
What 's that ?
Let 's go .
What is it about tower blocks and shopping trolleys ?
Stop taIking. lt 's a Iong way up .
( SeIena ) Do you need a break ?
- You ? - No .
Now I do need a break .
What 's up ?
Nothin ' .
I got a headache .
- Bad ? - Pretty bad .
- Why didn 't you say something before ? - l didn 't think you 'd give a shit .
You 've got no fat on you and all you 've had to eat is sugar .
So you 're crashing .
There isn 't a Iot we can do about that
except pump you full of painkillers and give you more sugar . As for sugar ,
Pepsi or LiIt ?
Do you have any Tango ?
actually , I did have a can of Tango somewhere .
( screech )
Quiet ! That 's an infected .
Oh no , they 're in . Move !
Wait up , selena !
Wait for me , please !
please , selena ! please !
- Wait for me ! - Come on !
- Run ! - Wait !
please ! For fuck 's sake !
- selena ! - ( screams )
Down the corridor . flat 1 57 . Move !
Thank you . Thank you .
Open the door !
- Open up ! - Where 's Dad ?
What ?
- Open the fucking door ! - Where 's Dad ?
Let them in , Hannah . Let them inside .
Go in . Go in !
( Frosty the Snowman playing )
So , I 'm Frank , anyway .
Jim .
- selena . - selena . Good to meet you .
This is my daughter Hannah .
Come on , sweetheart . Say hello .
Come on .
So ...
This is great . Just great .
calls for a celebration , I 'd say .
Why don 't you all sit down and ...
Hannah , what have we got to offer ?
We 've got Mum 's crème de menthe .
Great . Crème de menthe .
Oh , yeah . Look , sit , please .
Get comfortable .
- ( Frank ) Where are the bloody glasses ? - middle cupboard .
Nah , the good ones. lt 's a celebration .
Top cupboard .
So this is your place ?
It 's nice .
There .
I know it isn 't much but , well , cheers .
Cheers .
( groans )
You OK in there , Jim ?
Yeah .
Sorry we couldn 't spare the water .
Same with the toilet . The flush doesn 't work .
You 'II have to use the bucket .
Have to empty it each morning .
Just chuck it over the balcony . No mod cons here .
It 's fine .
Listen , it 's late . We 're gonna turn in .
We have a spare room .
In there .
Are you and selena ... ?
No . No , no , no .
Um ...
I 'II take the living room. lt 's fine .
Right .
No , I mean , yeah .
So , um ...
- Goodnight , then . - Yeah . Goodnight , Frank .
Very spruce .
- Very shredded . - Yeah .
- So what do you make of them ? - well , they 're desperate .
probably need us more than we need them .
I think they 're good people .
- Good people ? - Yeah .
You should be more concerned about whether they 're gonna slow you down .
- Because if they slowed you down ... - l 'd leave them behind .
- ln a heartbeat . - Yeah .
I wouldn 't .
Then you 're gonna wind up getting yourself killed .
I 'm gonna get some sleep .
selena ...
You think I don 't get it , but I do get it .
And I know I 'd be dead already if I hadn 't met you .
Sure .
No , look ...
I mean , thank you .
And I mean , sure .
Goodnight , Jim .
Goodnight .
We lost water pressure three weeks ago .
I thought we 'd be OK with the water from the other flats . Cisterns and tanks .
But it vanishes so quick you wouldn 't believe .
You drink it ,
it evaporates ,
turns stagnant .
They 're all empty .
Hasn 't rained in ten days .
You can set up a plastic sheet to catch dew and condensation .
Saw it on TV once , but I can 't make it work .
You 'd never think it .
Needing rain so badly .
Not in fucking england !
Jim , we 're not going to be able to stay here .
- There 's been no broadcasts for weeks . - Just listen .
( man on radio ) Salvation is here . The answer to Infection is here .
If you can hear this , you 're not alone .
There are others like you . There are other survivors .
We are soldiers and we are armed .
Oh , my God . soldiers .
- Quiet . There 's more . - Our location is the 42nd blockade , M602 ,
27 miles northeast of Manchester .
- You must find us . Salvation is ... - Now it just repeats .
- lt 's a recording ? - Yeah , it 's a recording .
But this is where it 's telling us to go .
Just there .
The way things are , we might need two or three days to get up there .
" We " ?
Sound carries in this flat . Me and Hannah do need you more than you need us .
- Look , I didn 't ... - No , it 's OK. lt 's the truth .
I can 't leave the block if it 's the two of us .
Something might happen to me . Hannah 'd be aIone. I couldn 't risk it .
But with other people ...
lf it 's a recording , the soldiers who made it could be dead .
- lt 's possible . - That stuff about the answer to infection ...
There is no answer ! It 's already done all the damage it can !
- Maybe they have a cure . - Maybe they 've got nothing .
- The only way to find out is to reach them . - We could die trying , Frank !
Or die here .
And anyway , it isn 't true what Dad said . You need us just the same as we need you .
We need each other .
And we 'II never be safe in the cities . The soldiers could keep us safe .
So we have to try and get there .
Get there how ?
Just so you know , I don 't take checks or credit cards .
- ( Frank ) What do you think ? - lt 's the most direct route .
Then we should take the indirect route . The one in daylight and not underground .
( Frank ) Let 's just get it done .
( Jim ) No , no .
No . See , this is a really shit idea .
You know why ? Because it 's obviously a shit idea .
So we 're gonna drive into the tunnel full of fucking smashed cars ...
lt 's really fucking obviously a shit idea !
hold on !
Dad !
( screaming and laughing )
Fuck !
The world 's worst place to get a flat .
Agreed. I think we 'd better do this quick .
I 've got the wheel . You 're on the jack .
Do you hear that ? Hey , hey , do you hear that ?
Hear what ?
( Hannah ) Right , I 've done it .
Dad ?
( scrabbIing sounds )
- Jesus Christ ! - ( Hannah screaming )
Fucking rats !
They 're running from the infected .
Move it !
Forget the jack , Hannah . There 's no time . Just lift , everyone .
Grab hold ! One , two , three , lift !
Lift , lift !
- ( SeIena ) Don 't look at them ! Don 't look ! - ( Jim ) I can see them ! They 're coming !
( screeching )
Come on , Hannah !
almost .
- Get the tire on , Hannah ! - l 'm trying .
Three , two , one ,
drop it !
- Get in the car ! - Come on !
- Frank , drive ! - Move it , Frank !
( Jim ) Whoo !
Goodbye , you fuckers !
Frank , stop the cab .
Let 's shop .
( Frank making engine noises )
You ...
( Jim ) Anybody seen any buns ?
Hmm. irradiated .
Don 't take anything that needs to be cooked , OK ?
I think you can eat that raw .
Decaffeinated coffee ...
Put that back .
Can 't just take any crap .
If I never see another chocolate bar again , it 'II be too soon .
Not counting Terry 's chocolate Orange !
Now , single malt , 1 6-year-oId . " Dark , full flavor . "
" Warm but not aggressive . "
- ( Hannah and selena laughing ) - " Peaty aftertaste . "
" Takes out the fire but leaves in the warmth . "
Either we do this now or we 're walking .
Not you .
- Stay close , Jim . - What ?
You heard .
Where are you going ?
We 've got enough food , Jim .
We don 't have any cheeseburgers .
( quietly ) Like going on holidays with your aunt !
Oh , Jesus .
hello ?
I hate you !
Find anything ?
- Find anything , Jim ? - No ! Let 's get outta here .
OK , we 're done here .
OK , Hannah .
Easy . Brake !
Brake , brake !
Out .
( SeIena ) Mmmm ! Oh my God !
I can , Iike , taste the vitamin C.
Mmmm , the raisins are so moist .
What did you say ?
The raisins . They 're so moist .
Look over here .
Like a family .
( Hannah ) Do you think they 're infected ?
( Frank ) No .
They 're doing just fine .
Come on . Let 's eat !
Know what I was thinking ?
That you 'II never hear another piece of original music again .
You 'II never read a book that hasn 't already been written ,
or see a film that hasn 't already been shot .
Um ... that 's what you were thinking .
No .
I was thinking I was wrong .
About what ?
AII the death .
AII this shit .
It doesn 't really mean anything to Frank and Hannah because ...
well , she 's got her dad and he 's got his daughter . So ...
Cheeky monkey !
I was wrong when I said staying alive is as good as it gets .
See , that 's what I was thinking .
Was it ?
Mm . You stole my thought .
Sorry .
That 's OK .
You can keep it .
It 's getting late . We 'd better stay here for the night .
I can 't sleep .
Me neither .
Doesn 't feel safe , does it ?
Outside like this .
I think we 're safe enough .
selena didn 't seem to have any trouble .
Yeah , I noticed that .
Hey , selena ...
What ? What is it ?
How 'd you get to sleep ?
bloody hell . Must 've needed a hell of a prescription for that lot .
I didn 't need a prescription . I qualified as a chemist .
Oh , great . valium .
Not only will we be able to get to sleep
but if we 're attacked in the middle of the night , we won 't even care .
- Two each . - Not for me , thanks .
Can I , Dad ?
I don 't think so , sweetheart .
please ?
- No . - l can 't sleep .
Come on , Frank . Let her live a little .
- Give her half of one . - AII right . We 're on .
Night-night .
You 're a big softie , Frank .
Frank ?
Hannah ?
hello ? hello !
hello !
hello ! hello !
( mumbles )
Shh ...
You 're having a bad dream , that 's all .
Thanks , Dad .
( car horn )
Come on , sIeepyhead .
Come on , Babe Ruth .
( Frank ) Hurry up .
- Did I miss breakfast ? - ( SeIena ) You 'II sleep through anything .
( Jim ) Did you have a fry-up ?
( Frank ) We 'II stop at a pub on the way . Door !
( radio ) Our location is the 42nd blockade , the M602 ,
27 miles northeast of Manchester .
You must find us . please !
salvation is here .
The answer to Infection is here .
Must be Manchester .
The whole of Manchester , the whole city .
No fire crews to put it out .
42nd blockade .
This is it .
I don 't understand , Dad . Did they leave ?
- l don 't like this. I think we should go . - No !
vehicles . We should check the vehicles . There has to be something .
Nothing .
I can 't believe it .
Frank ...
Frank !
- We have to go . - Yeah .
Go fucking where ? !
( cawing )
Get out of it .
Get out of it !
Dad , are you all right ?
Yeah , I 'm fine , sweetheart .
Sorry I lost my temper .
Hannah ...
I Iove you very much .
- What ? - Keep away from me .
Stay where you are .
- Dad ? - Keep away from me ! Keep away from me !
Keep away ! Keep away ! Keep away !
- Dad ! - Keep away ! Keep away !
( Hannah ) What 's wrong ? Dad !
Jim ! Jim , he 's infected !
- No ! - Now , Jim ! Now !
- Jim , kill him ! Jim ! - Dad !
kill him !
Stay away from him !
Keep away from the body !
Dad ?
( man ) Three survivors . One male , two female .
I repeat , one male , two female .
ETA , 1 5 .
Put the kettle on .
I 'm Major Henry West .
- welcome . - Jim .
hello , Jim .
hello .
well , we 've got beds with clean sheets and a boiler that produces hot water .
So you can all have a shower .
You look like you need one . please .
It ain 't funny. I got loads of cooking to do , you fucking Doris !
Run him over !
( Jim ) How is she doing ?
She 's lost her dad , Jim . That 's how she is .
It 's all fucked .
What do you mean ?
Oh , don 't do that . Come on , come on , come on .
Hey , don 't do that .
Hannah is what Frank says she is . Tough , strong , and she 'II cope just like I 'II cope .
- Just like you 'II cope . - l don 't want her to have to fucking cope .
I want her to be OK .
When Hannah had her dad it was OK .
It was OK for them and it was OK for us .
Now it 's all just fucked .
So you heard our broadcast ?
- Yeah , we did . - We must be a disappointment .
You were hoping for a full brigade . An army base with helicopters and a field hospital .
- We were just hoping for ... - The answer to infection .
Yeah .
As I said before , it 's here . Though it may not be quite what you imagined .
- Just feel lucky to have found you . - You were lucky .
The fire drove hundreds of infected out of Manchester .
The surrounding area 's teeming with them .
But don 't worry .
You 're quite safe here .
flat terrain all round the house . FIoodIights which we 've rigged up to a generator .
High perimeter wall which helps .
And we 've been lacing the ground with tripwires and land mines .
You wouldn 't want to mow the lawn , but if they get in , we hear them .
Secondary to protection , our real job is to rebuild . Start again .
The belly of the house . The heart .
A wood-fired boiler providing us with hot water . The first step towards civilization .
The kitchen .
Here you are. I 'II swap you .
- Now don 't be throwing it . - Here , give us some .
Don 't be fighting . will you put that back ? Put it back .
Jones , our resident tin opener .
- What are you cooking , Jones ? - Surprise , sir .
I can 't wait .
And lastly , meet mailer .
mailer , Jim .
Jim , mailer .
Got infected two days ago .
mitchell managed to knock him out cold and we got a chain round his neck .
Keeping him alive ?
The idea was to Iearn something about infection .
Have him teach me .
And has he ?
In a way .
He 's telling me he 'II never bake bread .
Farm crops ,
raise livestock .
He 's telling me he 's futureIess .
And eventually he 'II tell me how long the infected take to starve to death .
( singing )
You 'II have to wait and see
Hope it 's chips , it 's chips
We hope it 's chips , it 's chips
( cheering )
Hat .
So , what have we here ?
Tinned ham , tinned peas , tinned beans and ...
- ( man ) Nice one , Doris ! - OmeIet !
- lt 's a feast , Jones . - Honor of our guests .
AbsoIuteIy. I was going to propose a toast
but this omelet will do just as well .
- To new friends . - ( all ) New friends .
Jones , did you notice while cooking that these eggs were off ?
I thought the salt might cover the taste , sir .
Get rid of it .
( man ) Doris , you twat .
I don 't suppose you can cook , can you ?
I can 't tell you how badly we need someone with a little flair in the kitchen .
What a fucking disappointment .
I saw those eggs , I thought it was Christmas .
We 'II have eggs again . Once everything 's back to normal .
You muppet ! Look at him , eh ?
He 's still waiting for Marks and Spencer 's to reopen .
- You don 't know nothing . - l think bill 's got a point .
If you look at the whole life of the planet ,
we ...
you know , Man has only been around for a few blinks of an eye .
So if the infection wipes us all out ,
that is a return to normality .
- That what you meant , bill ? - Yeah , yeah .
Have you met our New Age sergeant ?
Our spiritual guru .
tell me , FarreII , exactly why did you join the army in the first place ?
This is what I 've seen in the four weeks since infection .
people killing people .
Which is what I saw in the four weeks before infection ,
the four weeks before that ...
As far back as I care to remember , people killing people .
Which to my mind puts us in a state of normality now .
- You 're not eating ? - l don 't want to eat .
You must eat , Hannah .
I don 't want to eat . I want to bury my dad .
He 's one of the people you 're talking about .
( explosion )
Let 's go , Iet 's go , Iet 's go !
Move !
Move ! Move ! Move !
( siren )
Enemy in front !
Mick , I fucking got one !
What do you want , a fucking sweetie ? Keep shooting , you cunt !
Fucking hell ! He bounced !
Cease fire !
I ain 't never seen that in my Iife !
- Report clear ! - Fucking hell !
- clear . - clear .
Yeah , yeah , clear .
Oh , hello !
( wolf whistle )
Listen , sweetheart , you ain 't gonna be needing this anymore .
Cos you got me to protect you now .
You wanna get your hands on a really big chopper , you just come and see me .
Fuck you !
- That 's an offer , Mitch . - Give her some .
How about right now ?
mitchell !
Easy , tiger . You don 't wanna go picking a fight with me , son .
Sergeant FarreII !
- mitchell , first action on . - Resecure the perimeter .
Then get to it . Jones , Bedford , go with him .
slow down .
- Sergeant ? - Sir .
clear the bodies off the lawn .
The rest of you , go with him .
My apologies .
Drink ?
Look , we 're grateful , OK ?
We 're very grateful for your protection but if we 're gonna stay here ...
- Who have you killed ? - No one .
Who have you killed ? You wouldn 't be alive now if you hadn 't killed somebody .
I killed ... I killed a boy .
A child ?
Yes .
But you had to . Otherwise he 'd have killed you .
survival .
I understand .
I promised them women .
What ?
Eight days ago I found Jones with his gun in his mouth .
He said he was going to kill himself because there was no future .
What could I say to him ?
We fight off the infected or we wait until they starve to death and then what ?
What do nine men do except wait to die themselves ?
I moved us from the blockade , I set the radio broadcasting
and I promised them women .
Because women mean a future .
selena ! Hannah !
- What is it ? - We have to go .
- Jim , wait ! - No time ! Come on !
Come on !
We get in the car and we go !
No ! You 're not going to keep them here ! You 've got to let them go !
You can 't keep them here ! Stay where you are !
I 'm not gonna let you keep them here !
You can 't do this !
Right , get him !
I want to give you a chance .
You can be with us .
But I can 't let them go .
OK , Jim ? OK .
Him too .
( FarreII ) Smithers says " Women and semen don 't mix . "
And Mr Burns says " We all know what you think , Smithers . "
And that was my favorite joke in The Simpsons .
That 's what they 're doing a few hundred miles away , across the channel ,
across the atlantic . Eating dinner and watching the fucking Simpsons !
They 're sleeping in their beds next to their wives .
But we 're here chained to a fucking radiator because the OC has gone insane !
Starting the world again when the rest of the world hasn 't even stopped .
Just imagine , just think about it .
How could infection cross the oceans ?
How could it cross the mountains and the rivers ? It can be stopped .
Right now TVs are playing and planes are flying
and the rest of the world is continuing as fucking normal .
Think ! actually think about it .
What would you do with a diseased little island ?
They quarantined us .
" There is no infection . It 's just people killing people . " He 's insane !
Time to go .
Quarantine ?
- please ... - believe me , I 'm not interested .
You see , I 'm gonna have the black one . And I 'm gonna make her squirm .
mitchell , I swear to God it 's gonna end badly for you .
Move .
Come on , move ! Get up !
Get up , you cunt ! Fucking move !
Get up !
Move your fucking arse !
( FarreII ) Come on then , you fucking pansies . Do me first .
( Jones ) No , Mitch . Mitch , just use the gat .
- ( FarreII ) So you 're gonna stick me ? - ( Jones ) Shoot ' em !
- ( MitcheII ) Why ? - Because it 's fucking quicker !
( FarreII ) ls that how you 'd let your sergeant go out , Jones ?
- l 'II shoot them ! - No , you won 't .
You 'II let him stick me ? Like a fucking dog ?
I 'm gonna enjoy this .
You stupid cunt ! What are you doing ? You wanna shoot me ?
- You wanna shoot me ? I 'II kill you ! - Where 's he fucking gone ?
Fuck it ! Get up ! Get after him !
- Jones , move it ! - l can see him ! I can see him !
Where are you ?
- Can you see him ? - Through there !
( gunfire )
Oh no . We 're fucked .
We 're fucked !
relax .
He 's over the wall . He 's got no vehicle .
And no shooter .
He 's dead .
( thunder )
( West ) The first thing we 're going to do is make you look more presentable .
The lady of the house has an extensive wardrobe
which she certainly has no use for .
You can 't do it to Hannah .
Go to the master bedroom , pick out a wide selection .
Yes , sir .
( Hannah ) No ...
( man ) Ladies ...
- lt 's only dressing up ! - No ! selena !
- l thought girls liked dressing up . - Expensive dresses .
( Hannah ) SeIena !
Whoa , whoa , relax !
selena !
selena ! selena !
You need to leave me alone with Hannah . OK ?
- Listen , right . The OC wants ... - He wants us to dress up nice .
If you want us to get changed , you have to leave the room . OK ?
It 's just polite .
Yeah , all right .
AII right .
Come on , lads . Let 's leave the room .
We 're gonna eat these , Hannah , OK ? Come on . Eat these .
Are you trying to kill me ?
No , sweetheart .
I 'm making you not care . OK ?
What you doing ? !
( siren )
- Someone 's at the blockade ! - Jim !
Move !
Stay here and put the dresses on .
Let 's go ! Go !
He went over the wall . We thought he 'd be dead .
Shut up , Jones ! Stay here .
Davis ?
( engine fails )
Fuck it !
( gunfire )
- What was that ? - Lightning .
I heard something .
It sounded like a claymore to me .
AII right , I 'II go and hit the floods , take a butcher 's .
girls ,
keep an eye on him , will ya ?
Those pills ,
I think they 're having an effect .
I can feel them . And ...
I don 't feel sleepy .
But ...
They 've been a Iong time .
What are you gonna do if they don 't come back ?
would you be the officer if Henry was dead ?
is that the way it works ?
Shut up .
I don 't think they are coming back . I think they 've been killed .
- l said shut up ! - Hannah ...
They 're dead .
And you 're gonna be next .
- Get up ! - Whoa !
We 're gonna get out of here . Stay with it , Hannah .
Don 't worry. I feel fine . really .
Get him off me !
It 's Jones ! It 's Jones !
Oi ! Where the fuck are you going ? What 's all the fucking shouting about ?
( screaming )
Don 't just stand there , you soppy cunt ! Get after them !
You two , in there ! Move !
( wheezing )
Come on , then !
What the fuck you gonna do now ?
( screaming )
Come on up !
col !
- Defend these stairs with your fucking life ! - Hannah !
- mailer 's loose . - Hannah !
( screech )
( screeching and wheezing )
Sorry ...
- Sir ... - Shh .
Shh .
Hannah ?
( screech )
selena ?
I haven 't got any bullets . I haven 't got any fucking bullets !
Don 't fucking leave me !
Come on !
Move !
Move ! Move !
It 's just you and me now , darlin ' . But don 't worry , I 'II get you out of here .
Then we 'II find a nice little fucking place somewhere . Just you and me .
And we 'II live happy ever after , eh ?
( screaming )
That was longer than a heartbeat .
Jim ?
Listen . Listen. it 's not all fucked .
We 're gonna be OK. lt 's not all fucked .
- l 've got to explain something . - Shut up .
It 's gonna be OK .
Hannah , it 's OK ! He 's not infected .
But I thought he was biting you .
I was kissing her . Are you stoned ?
- lt 's a Iong story . - ( screeching )
We have to get out of here . Come on !
Come on ! Move !
You killed all my boys .
Wait ...
Hannah !
Hannah ? Hannah !
Get in .
They 're locked .
The gates are locked !
Fucking do it !
Come on , Jim , breathe ! Fucking breathe !
Not the curtains as well .
( man speaking on radio )
You looked all right in this , you know .
It 's coming !
- You definitely heard it ? - Yeah !
- l can 't hear anything ! - l told you , I heard it !
( distant aircraft )
Go .
Do you think he saw us this time ?
english - US - SDH